calamitiesofnature.com 2012-12-29

# Calamities of Nature - Privacy Policy

**GENERAL PRIVACY POLICY FOR VISITORS OF WWW.CALAMITIESOFNATURE.COM**

Calamities of Nature is dedicated to protecting the privacy of the visitors to www.calamitiesofnature.com. We have provided this privacy policy so you know how your information is used.

We collect information based on your IP address, including your country of origin, the type of web browser you use, what search engines you may have used to find www.calamitiesofnature.com, or what site may have referred you. This information is used for tracking purposes only, and it is never provided to any other entities.

**MAILING LIST PRIVACY POLICY**

When you sign up for our mailing list, we will retain your e-mail address. Calamities of Nature will use your supplied address to provide you with any pertinent news items relating to the site that we issue from time to time. We will not share the information you provide with any other entity.

If at any time you wish to remove your information from our records, please send an e-mail to calamitiesofnature@gmail.com with the title "unsubscribe." We will promptly remove you from our mailing list.

**PRIVACY POLICY WITH REGARD TO USE E-MAIL CONTACT**

When you submit an e-mail to site author Tony Piro or any other persons speaking on behalf of Calamities of Nature to request additional information about Calamities of Nature or its services, the information you provide is used solely as a means to provide you with that information. Your information is used only for responding to your request and is never provided to any other entities.

**PRIVACY QUESTIONS**

If you have any questions with relation to our privacy practices or the web site itself, feel free to contact Tony Piro at calamitiesofnature@gmail.com.
